<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Angela&#39;s personal learning blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Angela&#39;s personal learning blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Songs Lyrics</title>
      <link>/post/christmas-songs-lyrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/christmas-songs-lyrics/</guid>
      <description>Christmas songs lyrics Today I am going to look at the lyrics of Christmas songs. A certain song that has been around for many many years is not being played on local radios this year as the lyrics are suddenly considered politically incorrect or following the me too movement. As I am also learning text mining at the moment I thought it might be a good idea to have a look at the songs we hear at this time of year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Text Mining </title>
      <link>/post/learning-text-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/learning-text-mining/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dplyr tips</title>
      <link>/post/dplyr-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dplyr-tips/</guid>
      <description>here I am going to put all the different things I have learned in dplyr for easy reference.
more tips from Rladies, #rstats etc from twitter or just new things to me!
%T&amp;gt;% from magrittr where you can print or some other function with pipes without breaking up your code
plotly can create plot in ggplot and then put it in a call to plotly plotly::ggplotly to create interactive graphics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up the blog</title>
      <link>/post/setting-up-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/setting-up-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>I am referring primarily to the Blogdown book by Yihue to build this website. I am also working off Alison Premane Hills tutorial &amp;lsquo;Up and Running with blogdown. A workshop for the Portland R User Group&amp;rsquo;. [slides and link](&amp;ldquo;https://apreshill.rbind.io/talk/blogdown-meetup/&amp;quot;)
blogdown::new_site() command to build a site
serve_site() I need to find out when to use serve_site() instead of hugo_build() serve_site() seems to do the trick for me. When I run this command, I then can drag my public folder directly into the netlify page to manually deploy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why am I doing this?</title>
      <link>/post/why-am-i-doing-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/why-am-i-doing-this/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to take the advice I keep coming across on twitter to start a blog and document your learning. The main reason for me is to keep track of the various courses and projects I am working on and have one central place to find everything as I spend far too much time trying to find something I have done before! I started building the blog 2 months ago but then went back to other courses and tutorials and projects which I have kept locally on my computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What am I at?</title>
      <link>/post/what-am-i-at/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/what-am-i-at/</guid>
      <description>At the moment I have working through the Tidy Text Mining in R book by Julia Silge and David Robinson
 Tidy Text Mining in R
I am working through the Tidy Text Mining in R book by Julia Silge and David Robinson. Trying to replicate the examples using other texts. Trying to make sure I understand each function.
 Joining Data in Dplyr
 Dplyr Tips
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>